So,Kevin,what do you think?
So,Kevin, 你认为怎么样?
Elena,I haven't met her yet,have I?
Elena, 我还没见过她呢!
I know.But does she sound interesting?
我知道. 但她听起来是不是很有意思?
Yes.From what you've told me,she sounds lovely.
Yes. 从你说的来看, 她挺可爱的.
She said the same thing about you.
她也是这么说你的.
What?
When I described you...
在我描述你时...
What did you say?
你都说了些什么?
Well,you know...
Well, 你知道的...
Come on,Elena.
I said,"He's tall.He's good-looking.
我说:"他个头高高的. 长的挺帅.
He's nice.And he's very funny."
人不错. 而且非常有趣."
If you can understand his accent.
要是你能听得懂他的口音的话.
Did you tell her I used to work as a physicist?
你有没有告诉她我以前是一名物理学家?
Good on you,mate.
你太棒了,伙计.
Kevin,you used to be a physicist?
Kevin, 你过去是物理学家吗?
No,but it sounds so impressive,doesn't it?
不是, 但这样会让人印象很深刻,对不对?
Dean.
Kevin.
Elena.
Elena!
Heather!
Dean!
And you must be Heather.
你一定是Heather.
Heather,this is Kevin.
Heather, 这是Kevin.
Right,the physicist.Nice to meet you.
Right, 物理学家. 很高兴见到你.